<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="97">
	<author>Glowins Modschmiede</author>
  <version>2.0.0.1</version>
	<title>
		<en>Cultivator Settings</en>
		<de>Grubbereinstellungen</de>
  </title>
  <description>
  <en>
<![CDATA[
Cultivator settings

Description: 
Many cultivators from the game can be operated at different working depths in reality, depending on the setting.
In the game, individual cultivators also have the option of being set to “flat cultivator” or “normal cultivator”.

With this modification, all cultivators get this option and can also be set to “deep cultivator”.
They can be configured in the store to a fixed working mode or as a variable cultivator, which can then be switched via the working mode (extra cost: €2,500). If a cultivator is to be used unchanged, this can also be configured in the store.

Soil cultivation with the deep cultivator replaces plowing.

Key combinations: 
The cultivators are switched via the standard function “Switch working mode”

Change Log V2.0.0.1 
- Fixed: Nil-condition that could occur occasionally at game/server start

GitHub link: https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_CultivatorSettings
Further ideas or requests are welcome at https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_CultivatorSettings
]]>
		</en>	
		<de>
<![CDATA[
Grubbereinstellungen

Beschreibung: 
Viele Grubber aus dem Spiel lassen sich in der Realität je nach Einstellung mit unterschiedlicher Arbeitstiefe betreiben.
Auch im Spiel verfügen einzelne Grubber über die Möglichkeit, auf "Flachgrubber" oder "normaler Grubber" eingestellt zu werden.

Mit dieser Modifikation erhalten alle Grubber diese Möglichkeit und können darüber hinaus auch auf "Tiefengrubber" eingestellt werden.
Sie können im Shop auf einen festen Arbeitsmodus konfiguriert werden, oder als variabler Grubber, der dann über den Arbeitsmodus umgeschaltet werden kann (Extrakosten: 2.500 €). Soll ein Grubber unverändert genutzt werden, ist auch das im Shop konfigurierbar.

Die Bodenbearbeitung mit dem Tiefengrubber ersetzt das Pflügen.

Tastenkombinationen: 
Das Umschalten der Grubber erfolgt über die Standard-Funktion "Arbeitsmodus umschalten"

Change Log V2.0.0.1 
- Behoben: Nil-Bedingung, die vereinzelt beim Spiel-/Serverstart auftreten konnte

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_CultivatorSettings
Weitere Ideen oder Wünsche werden gerne unter https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_CultivatorSettings entgegengenommen
]]>
		</de>	    
 	</description>	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>icon_CultivatorSettings.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
    	<sourceFile filename="cultivatorSettingsRegister.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n>
		<text name="text_DC_configuration">
            <en>Cultivator Setting</en>
            <de>Grubbereinstellung</de>
        </text>
		<text name="deepMode">
            <en>Cultivator is configured as a subsoiler now</en>
            <de>Grubber ist nun als Tiefengrubber eingestellt</de>
        </text>
		<text name="normalMode">
            <en>Cultivator is configured as a cultivator now</en>
            <de>Grubber ist nun als normaler Grubber eingestellt</de>
        </text>
        <text name="shallowMode">
            <en>Cultivator is configured as a shallow cultivator now</en>
            <de>Grubber ist nun als Flachgrubber eingestellt</de>
        </text>
        <text name="mode">
        	<en>Mode: %s</en>
        	<de>Modus: %s</de>
        </text>
		<text name="deepModeShort">
            <en>Deep Cultivation</en>
            <de>Tiefes Grubbern</de>
        </text>
        <text name="normalModeShort">
        	<en>Normal Cultivation</en>
        	<de>Normales Grubbern</de>
        </text>
        <text name="shallowModeShort">
            <en>Shallow Cultivation</en>
            <de>Flaches Grubbern</de>
        </text>
        <text name="text_DC_deep">
            <en>Subsoiler</en>
            <de>Tiefengrubber</de>
        </text>
         <text name="text_DC_shallow">
            <en>Shallow cultivator</en>
            <de>Flachgrubber</de>
        </text>
        <text name="text_DC_normal">
            <en>Cultivator</en>
            <de>Grubber</de>
        </text>
        <text name="text_DC_off">
            <en>Default game setting</en>
            <de>Original-Einstellung</de>
        </text>
        <text name="text_DC_ISOBUS">
            <en>Switchable</en>
            <de>Umschaltbar</de>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
